hellopoetry.com 2011-05-28

# Privacy policy — Hello Poetry

## Privacy policy

We respect your right to privacy.

We will not give your name or personal information to third parties.

### Email

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us.

You will also receive certain email notifications (forwarded messages, etc.), for which you may opt-out.

We may send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.

### Technology / Security

Hello Poetry uses _cookies_ to help (anonymously) recognize you as a repeat visitor and to track traffic patterns on our site. We use this information to make Hello Poetry more user-friendly.

Hello Poetry may obtain IP _addresses_ from users. We will use this information to monitor and prevent fraud, diagnose problems, and (anonymously) estimate demographic information.

We use a variety of security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Your personal information is stored behind firewalls and is only accessible by a limited number of people who are required to keep the information confidential.

Regardless of these efforts by us, no data transmission over the public Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

### Voluntary Disclosure

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose in public areas becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by other users. You should exercise caution before disclosing your personal information via these public venues.

### Wrap-up

Hello Poetry reserves the right to update this privacy policy at anytime. Updates to our privacy policy will be sent to the email address that you have provided us or posted prominently on the website.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law).

To modify or delete any or all of the personal information you have provided to us, please login and update your profile.

_People under 13 are not permitted to use Hello Poetry on their own, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for their use of the site._

### Questions

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at: [@hellopoetry.com](mailto:)
